Crusader Kings II is an historical strategy game
I'm not sure when it takes place
I think it is before Pearl Harbor
I wanna say in the 50's
The goal is to take over the entire world which is not that hard if you play as a
as a powerful country like France or the Holy Roman Empire
But I like a bit of a challenge so I am going to play as the county of Cornwall
The only thing we got going for us is the fact that our enemies might underestimate us
because we named our country after a vegetable
I'd like to remind you that the game is very slow so taking over everything might up towards 50-60 hours
[transcription incomplete]
That took 20 minutes, Cornwall is surprisingly overpowered
I'll tell you how I did it, we'll just wait for the victory screen... but it's not showing up
Did I miss some place?
Ah, this island named "Some place", how convinient.
Who is the ruler?
Steven?
There is an island underneath the Arabian peninusla and it's ruled by a guy named Steven
His traits are "kind", "charitable", "genius", "strong", "attractive"?
Fuck this guy
But I can't just declare war on him because I need a better reason then the fact that I don't like his smug face
So I am going to have my chancelor fabricate a claim on the island. This shouldn't take very long...
... and where did he go?
Apparently he defected and then he and Steven got gay married in the middle ages
So that plan didn't work
The reason I can't just attack him is that we are both Catholics.
So I am going to switch from being a Catholic to worshipping a reindeer
Which is pretty weird because I am the pope, but now we can declare a holy war
12000 soldiers should be enough, I mean it's not a very big island
Steven, better pack your bags because you're moving into a prison cell
Huh... your minister of foreign affairs has decided to surrender. We surrendered... to Steven!?
Why do I even need a minister of foreign affairs there is only one other country
So now I can't attack him because we have a peace treaty
But there are other ways of taking out a threat. I am going to assassinate him.
I am going to pay a guard 294 gold to take him out
Steven accepted his faith. Good good.
Then the guard fell on his knees and began to cry
No that's not good.
Then they drank hot chocolate!?
Chocolate hadn't even been discovered yet!
Steven, I swear to reindeer I will end you
No, let's calm down. You know what? He's 47. Medicine hasn't improved since ancient Greece
he will die any die now of a paper cut or something, let's just wait him out
Ah, 1452. By now medicine had improved a lot. But still, if you had a minor heacache your left arm had to go
so I am just wondering how is it possible he survived to 432!?
That's it, I will just go back and raise the largest invasion force the world has ever seen
and no one will be able to stop me because I control the entire world
Are you ready Steven?
Are you ready for thy death?
... and I am getting invaded by the Aztecs...
I am not even surprised anymore
Aztecs are gone. Army is gone. Resources are gone
Surprisingly there hasn't been a single rebellion
Hmm, but you win Steven. I give up
You can have the rest of my gold
Wait... wait
Offer Vassalization?
Oh my reindeer, he fell for it!
Wait what just happened?
Died a natural death? Damnit!
Just give me my victory screen
And still nothing
Let me guess, everyone's love of Steven was the only thing keeping this empire together
Of course, oh this will be fun
So the empire collapsed and I am back to where I started, so I haven't actually lost anything
I can't help to think that if only I had been Stevens friend none of this would have happened
and maybe friendship... Hold on a minute!
Cornwall...
Europeans first encountered corn in the 16th century so how could they possible have named it...
Aliens
The county of Cornwall is a spaceship